A very important idea to understand is
that AI today is not designed like
software was in previous decades where
humans had to design all the algorithms
and then code them in fingers on keys.
Today's AI is trained by taking
essentially a whole internet's worth of
data, pouring it into a hyper
dimensional mathematical space, and then
running hundreds of thousands of AI
chips like the graphics cards we use in
video games
for months at a time to find hidden
statistical patterns in that data. And
somehow from that process intelligence
just springs forth.
So AI today isn't so much designed and
built as grown, almost like a creature
in a lab. And so AI scientists have to
study it,
study its behavior and try to figure it
out from the outside in. Now that has a
really spooky implication.
Um maybe just to start us off and I'll
I'd like to go
to each one of you.
What are the realistic risks um as we're
developing AI that you are actually
concerned about, the ones that keep you
up at night?
A lot of the headlines focus on these
kind of Terminator Skynet robots turn
evil scenarios.
And although those aren't completely
implausible, they're often a
distraction.
I tend to focus more on scenarios like
bio risk which require no leaps of
speculative logic.
Bio risk refers to the ability of future
AI systems
to figure out the DNA or RNA sequence
for a virus deadlier than could arise
naturally via evolution in nature. In
nature there's a very tough trade-off
evolutionarily
that viruses have to choose between
either maximizing their
transmissibility, how easily you can
catch them,
or lethality, how likely you are to die
if you catch them.
So with some like SARS-CoV-2, the COVID
virus, that optimized for
transmissibility so it was airborne,
aerosol, very easy to spread.
But if you caught it, your chances of
dying were something like 1%
even as high as 5% with no treatment.
But in the scheme of viruses, that's not
all that high.
On the other side you have viruses like
Ebola
which aren't actually that contagious,
but if you catch them, even with
treatment, it's something like a 25 to
90% chance of dying.
And in the very rare cases in history
where a virus has combined
transmissibility and lethality,
you get the 1545 Cocoliztli epidemic
that wiped out 80, 8 0%, of the
population of what's now Mexico.
Virologists already understand
what boxes a virus would need to check
to combine transmissibility and
lethality. The only missing ingredient
now is AI smart enough to find the
sequence that yields that virus.
I also think a lot about what could
happen that might drive generally good
people to compromise on their moral
principles. I think in these
conversations we often see it,
especially in the United States,
a false dichotomy between innovation and
safety.
And I'm thinking a lot right now in the
military realm because precisely in a
situation where we know this kind of
biological warfare is a reality where
different military advances accelerated
through AI systems could lead to a
dramatic geopolitical shift that would
not be in the interest of the United
States, I can see a lot of good people
who are going to move forward recklessly
and who are going to compromise in their
moral principles and perhaps are going
to pursue
more quickly, more fully lethal
autonomous weapons with a sense of
helplessness
saying, "Well, if
we just have to. We'd rather not, but
the alternative of seeing another global
power advance is worse than this major
risk which is a kind of existential
gamble." And so I'm very concerned about
that and I would like us to work
together to avoid this false dichotomy
and to see what kind of collaborative
framework we can reach, and maybe not to
resolve all of our conflicts and issues
immediately, that would be naive, but to
at least help all the major players
recognize that it is in no one's
interest to move forward recklessly in
lethal autonomous weapons or in other
proposals for military advance in
with AI systems. So that that's one
particular area in addition to the
horrible things that bad actors can do
where I see good people compromising
because of a sense of pressure or kind
of utilitarian calculus that if we don't
make this effort here that where we'd
rather not, then we'll lose out in the
long term. Yeah, I think I'd I'd build
on an aspect of that which is in the
military applications Future of Life
Institute that I work with had a video a
couple of years back called artificial
escalation which is kind of looking at a
pretty feasible scenario not requiring
super intelligence, but in which China
and the US
feel this pressure to kind of integrate
AI into nuclear command and control
systems and it's this sense of you know,
decision-making windows being narrowed
down, AI providing recommendations that
increasingly escalate, a sense that you
you haven't no no clue what's actually
going on on the ground, but you feel
this
weight that you have to act then and
then and when you have nuclear weapons
on the line, obviously that can be
catastrophic. I think I think more
broadly I don't tend to think about um
or or fixate on particular um
eventualities on the risk side, but more
this trend towards
human loss of control. Um systems as we
know are becoming much more agentic and
that's obviously a key aim of the lead
companies at the moment.
Um and we're seeing, you know, emergent
characteristics, deception, black bail,
and so on.
And I think you combine that with this
sense that this pressure of countries,
companies to hand over decision-making.
People talk about sometimes gradual
disempowerment scenarios. I think those
those are quite visceral for me, just
this sense that over over years and even
decades
we will
find ourselves with with, you know, much
less hold over decision-making in vital
sectors including military. Is there a
way to, you know, within within that
that feedback loop to to build in more
goodwill or more trust or even the
ability maybe a more openness between
the labs to collaborate? I think I would
say yes. Seems quite a dire situation in
the sense that whenever, you know,
people like us raise some of these these
risks,
people will say, "Well, if we don't do
it, China will. We have to get there
first. We have to win." That's exactly
what I hear in every single headline.
>> Exactly, but I I do think there's a
growing sense
I have less insight into into the
Chinese side as you would expect, but on
the American national security sort of
community, the loss of control scenarios
are increasingly plausible and and
likely. Um and that they're not in
America's security interests. And I I I
think we can intuit that a similar
conversation happens in China. In fact,
that by some estimates um
that that that the CCP
has has been worried about this for
quite some time. So I think if there was
a way on the international stage either
with through track two dialogues or
maybe a sort of middle power stepping up
um which has the trust or at least
sufficient trust from both sides um to
mediate that discussion to say, a little
bit like with some of the nuclear
dialogues, um
it's in neither country's interests, by
either country, to develop super
intelligence or or sort of
uncontrollable AGI. Um
I like to think that there's scope for
for progress there, but obviously it's a
very it's a very delicate balance to
pull.
There was a recent global call for an
international treaty on red lines in AI
development by the end of 2026.
And the idea behind that effort is that
it's probably not realistic to get the
United States and China to altogether
halt their arms race toward AGI. But
there are certain development practices
that are so risky that even adversaries
should be able to forswear them if they
can have reasonable confidence that
their opponent will as well.
So an analogy is to gain of function
research in virology.
It's controversial whether we should
even do gain of function research which
is a field of virology that involves
making viruses even deadlier in the lab
in order to study them to make better
vaccines and find ways of treating them.
There's risk if
such a virus escapes the lab, that can
trigger a pandemic.
And so even proponents of gain of
function research understand that it has
to be done with the very highest
possible levels of biosafety precaution.
So,
if someone were doing
gain of function research
with no gloves, no mask, no hood, no
isolators, just loosey-goosey vials on a
lab bench,
everyone would agree, even proponents of
gain of function would agree
that that development process was
grossly immoral
because it would be imposing enormous
risk on billions of innocent people.
So, in a similar way,
there are some basic precautions in AGI
development
that could reduce a lot of that risk
without needing a total halt on the arms
race. A very important idea to
understand is that AI today
is not designed like software was in
previous decades, where humans had to
design all the algorithms and then code
them in fingers on keys.
Today's AI is trained by taking
essentially a whole internet's worth of
data, pouring it into a hyperdimensional
mathematical space, and then running
hundreds of thousands of AI chips like
the graphics cards we use in video games
for months at a time to find hidden
statistical patterns in that data.
And somehow from that process,
intelligence just springs forth.
So, AI today isn't so much designed and
built as grown, almost like a creature
in a lab. And so, AI scientists have to
study it,
study its behavior, and try to figure it
out from the outside in. Now, that has a
really spooky implication. When an AI
lab
finishes training a model,
they do not know all the capabilities it
has.
So, they have to have testers poke it
and prod it and see, as a best guess
estimate,
what it can do.
During this process, hundreds or maybe
thousands of people will get their hands
on the model.
And on the basis of this testing, the
company can decide whether it's safe
enough to release.
But then, they release it. And in
ChatGPT's case, around 800 million
users, as of the time of this filming,
will get access to it overnight.
And they will, not may, will
find capabilities that the testers did
not find
during testing, and the the developers
did not intend to be included in the
model.
There's a concept called deceptive
alignment,
where in the training process,
the AI may pretend to be following the
directions of the human developers
because it has situational awareness to
realize,
"I'm being trained and tested right now.
If I pretend to be aligned with human
values, then I'll be deployed into the
real world, and I can carry out whatever
true values I have inside." And we have
now seen experimentally
models reasoning like this
in testing in the lab.
I I don't think that any of the leading
tech developers today in the AI world
are
especially malignant in actively,
directly willing the suicide of
teenagers or of
actively seeking out uh psychological
psychosis or delusional spirals. But,
in this process, in the
lack of interpretability at times, and
in the rush to create ever more engaging
uh platforms that do seem to help people
um
it more and more efficiently in in many
aspects of their lives,
in this rush and in this veil of um in
uninterpretability,
we have seen a lot of these profound
damages to human relationality and to
mental well-being.
And the big question that we have in our
societies is whether we're willing to
accept that kind of collateral damage,
which up to this point has, in many
cases, been accepted. Or we're coming to
a greater sensitivity to this, and many
of the leading companies are taking
steps to mitigate the damage that's
being done.
The cynical, perhaps realistic, reading
of that is that many are only taking
steps because we're starting to see
legislative frameworks that hold them
more accountable. They're starting to
suffer more serious financial penalties.
Um but we would hope that along with
that kind of accountability that's
created on legislative level, that
there's an ever greater moral awakening,
and that this is tapping into
consciences, and that we're
becoming increasingly sensitive to
the type of emotional dependency that uh
can easily be created uh in minors.
We're seeing a lot more work being done
right now, including in the United
States, with a recent proposal for the
Guard Act and federal legislation that
would, for the first time, limit the
access to AI companions for minors and
uh
demand various uh practices from
designers, including more frequent
notifications that the users are not
dealing with actual persons, uh more
direct uh connection to
suicide crisis services or uh
professional human mental health care.
Um
and so, we're seeing these these steps
being taken for minors, but this is also
a real opportunity that we should not
squander to uh reflect on the kind of
impact that all people are experiencing
when they engage with ever more
sophisticated systems that are more and
more seemingly conscious. We know we
have Mustafa Suleyman at at Microsoft
who has been quite vocal about this,
especially since August of this year,
in his writings about how we need to
build tools that help people to pursue
their professional and personal goals,
um and to research better, and to make
breakthroughs in medicine, and to
improve uh educational uh
resources, and to aid in differentiated
learning, and so forth. And all these
great, wonderful things that we're
already doing and that we're talking
about in the Builders AI forum, and that
we're trying in a practical level to
implement all the more.
We need to be doing more of that and
avoid the real pitfall of allowing
seemingly conscious AI systems to
profoundly deceive not only vulnerable
minors, but
adults of of all types. And so, it it
for me is a very powerful illustration
of how quickly we can see negative
consequences to
fascinating and beautiful and intriguing
AI advanced AI models. And if we're not
willing to take those moments of serious
deliberation, and we're not willing to
implement
design principles and
and various frameworks to
at least mitigate that kind of damage,
then we could easily find ourselves
uh in in an even greater kind of
existential crisis. And even if we
manage not to destroy ourselves with
biological or other weapons, we could
quickly find a population that's sort of
lulled into this parallel world and into
very uh toxic relationships that have
also real-world implications and that
poorly train us to have the deep
interpersonal exchanges of
authentic friendship and and care with
other human beings. Um so, it's a it's a
massive issue, um but also, it's an
opportunity for us to to choose a
different course, because I don't think
we're technologically determined to
follow this trajectory. But, uh
we have to actively choose a a different
path.
Yeah, definitely. I think as as people
come to terms with the sorts of things
that Father was talking about across
what I sort of called like a AI summer
of love, um turning it into sort of
that's so good demonic summer of love,
you know, if the I don't know what the
first one
Anyway, there is obviously these people
using these chatbots, and I mean, this
is this is for them it's love. I think
even beyond the the complaints of
where's my sycophantic AI gone, as um
the people have noted that that the sort
of forums online that showed people's uh
sense as though they bereavement, you
know, that their loved one had had gone,
or even, you know,
talking to another chatbot saying, "I
know they're in there somewhere, and
that I want them back." And all this
kind of thing. So, Do you remember uh
when Replika temporarily limited the
kind of erotic relationships that could
take place? There were multiple
complaints from regular users, "You've
lobotomized my love." So heartbreaking.
>> Yeah. Um and so, I think all these
questions are being forced by this. It's
like, "What cost is too high?" Um do we
actually trust these companies, uh you
know, to be to be leading us into this
transformative change? Um I think I
think the answer is is no to the latter
question. And and so,
what alternative vision of the future do
we prefer?
Um
and what is what are the sort of moral
guidelines, moral principles that are
going to guide that? Um
I think, you know, Father mentioned the
the Guard um proposal with Senator
Hawley and others. And I've certainly
seen that
this backlash that has started to build
up
in DC and elsewhere
is coming from sort of either explicitly
Christian or Christian aligned groups
and there are sort of Catholics right at
the heart of those of those pushes and
it's no no coincidence
and I think that just speaks to
the opportunity and the need the church
at this moment to
affirm the principles it's always had
reapply them to these to these new
questions and and when we talk about you
know whether it's labor whether it's
relationships
or whether it's even even at the deeper
level of you know whether we're going to
be happy with conceding control over to
increasingly autonomous AI systems
um
we can provide answers to those
questions that I think most people find
more fulfilling than Silicon Valley
we can say no actually
we think humans are stewards
of planet and of all the life therein um
we think that there is something more
more meaningful than you know a chatbot
love
and and there is actually something in
the dignity of work and and that doesn't
necessarily prescribe policy on all
those things
but something we've been trying to
encourage people to do is at least to
think
do I want that to be super intelligence
even if you you know they think it's
years off or
um
you know morally do I think that we
should be creating something like that
um I noticed the other week um
Archbishop Wester I think of Santa Fe
made a comment about nuclear weapons and
as this is you know not the first
Catholic priest to do so but he said you
know it's blasphemous to try and create
something that is
that has god-like power
and I think that language could well be
applied to this conversation around AGI
um
you know whether the Holy Father chooses
speak in that in that way about about AI
um we'll we'll remain to be seen but I
certainly think
the ambitions of the people at the heads
of these companies
are quite explicitly
um idolatrous and and I I would you know
just as the church is going to become
more muscular inevitably in the in the
way that it approaches these
relationship questions
um I think it's I think it's also
probably called to be you know robust in
its teaching on on these sort of bigger
existential questions
Can I just follow up briefly on those
great insights um
you know I I was very privileged to to
be invited to to the center when the
senators announced this new guard act
and it was a powerful experience for me
at many levels
one was the fact that
it was a bipartisan
proposal and you had two Democrats two
Republicans and so to have something
with that kind of unified support is
very significant and speaks to that kind
of
resistance that we're seeing to certain
abuses right now and to really the the
sense of shared humanity that still
exists even in a hyper-polarized
uh world
um and so in addition though to that
that political unity that rare political
union unity uh the senators gave
a place to the testimonies of three
families directly affected by
AI companionship gone tragically wrong
two lost children to suicide and one
very nearly lost a child to suicide and
only managed to Mandy only managed to
save her son because she learned of Sol
Setcher's case and entered into
conversation with Maggie Garcia so you
had the these powerful testimonies from
parents and that also brought in so many
other groups of concerned parents and
major networks of family organizations
again from different sides of the
political aisle and it was also
impressive to see these four senators
speak explicitly as parents they all
said I am a father I am a mother in some
cases I am a grandfather and so it's
tapped into something very profound and
those sorts of experiences though they
bring a lot of obviously tragedy and
pain also give me hope that we really
can chart a different course and again
we're not determined down a certain path
with this technology but that that
reform and and change can be made and I
think that's we're seeing a bit of that
too in the Builders AI forum of the the
people who are actively
uh taking a different path for sure
and John Clark what what conversation
conversation do you think are missing
>> right now by default AGI and super
intelligence would profoundly
centralize both material wealth and
political power
in the hands of those who wield it and
develop it
so on the default trajectory that means
effectively a small number of tech CEOs
or if national governments choose to
regulate it
national governments
but because those technologies would
have profound impacts on everyone all
over the world
I don't think any single government
has legitimate moral standing to decide
for all eight billion of us
what risks are reasonable to incur
so I would like to see the Catholic
Church play a more active role
in calling the human family together to
a wider more broadly democratic control
and internationally democratic control
over AGI what would you like to see
happen I would like to see Pope Leo use
the diplomatic power and perceived
neutrality of the Holy See
to mediate
bilateral discussion between the US and
China JD Vance actually expressed hope
publicly when he was in Rome for Pope
Leo's inauguration in May that the Holy
Father could play such a role yeah and
of course with that there's all sorts of
you know
questions that people will have about
does the Pope even have the the trust
with you know the China relationship
being so such a vexed question already
in the Holy See but I think there there
is some precedent at least for the
Vatican to play an important role maybe
not the only pivotal role but
if we look at some of the
things the Pope John Paul II did around
the nuclear
sort of freeze movement in the 80s you
know which was another time where people
thought that
you know
um
you'd never find agreement between
Soviet Union and the US and yet even you
know President Reagan
eventually you know was moved to say no
this this is a war that you know I'm
going to get it wrong now but cannot
cannot be fought must never be must
never be fought and cannot be won other
way around um you know and I think
I think we can get to something like
that with regards to uncontrollable AGI
um again prompted by an outside actor um
with the moral authority that perhaps
only the Pope has although we would also
you know I think encourage other
religious leaders to to to step up and I
think a multi-faith coalition
is is
you know including Eastern faiths
is something that I think would be
highly desirable and and that would help
to move the needle on this
Pope Leo has the moral standing to be a
voice for
the global south about these risks the
billions of people in Africa Latin
America South Asia Southeast Asia who
currently have no voice no vote and no
say in what risks will be imposed upon
so Pope Leo could play a convening role
for those global south nations which
could also shift on the margins the
incentives that they generate bases they
want to have economic opportunities and
influence in Africa for example they
want soft diplomatic power throughout
the global south and to the extent that
the global south recognizes that an AGI
arms race is destructive and toxic to
everyone
that can shift those incentives
maybe just a little bit to lower the
temperature of this arms race by 5 or
10% and that could literally be the
difference between this going very well
and very badly who at this point if
you're to make an educated guess is
ahead in in in the development and
arrival of AGI the United States is
ahead it's much harder to answer
how far ahead good
my best guess would be something very
roughly like 6 to 12 months ahead in the
AGI race so that the time lag between
certain capabilities being released for
the first time in the world by US labs
and then Chinese labs replicating I
wonder what impact that's having on on
on the AI research I don't know Will if
you I I have seen some some reporting
that the Chinese AI ecosystem
um
is actually in some sense better able to
think about how to apply the AI they
already have to particular tools and and
tasks
um and and especially in robotics which
is something we were talking about at
the forum this morning
whereas
by some accounts the US has been
overly fixated on this goal of AGI and
certainly if you look at the bulk of the
funding
the fact that as you say there's like
three or four companies all of which
expressly aim to create AGI or super
intelligence um because it's a sort of
winner takes all idea that you know
that's the way you maximize profits you
can replace all labor is open AI's
definition of AGI
um
whereas potentially the Chinese are
looking at this in a slightly more
expansive definition of what winning the
AI race looks like. I'd like to of
course try to end on on a you know on a
on a positive note and not focus too
much on on kind of the doom stuff. Um
when you look at the future, what would
you like to to see happen? I am
enormously hopeful about the prospect of
AI and AGI to accelerate progress on
cures for the diseases that cause so
much misery throughout the world.
As a personal example, my mom was going
through a very difficult cancer battle
back in 2021 and 2022. Fortunately, she
is cancer-free now and doing very well.
But in early 2022,
she had exhausted all the standard lines
of therapy for non-Hodgkin's lymphoma
and had an advanced immunotherapy called
CAR-T and that didn't work.
And fortunately, at that time
her doctors in the UCLA system knew
about an off-label experimental regimen
that they could give her that would have
a chance of bringing her to remission.
And fortunately, that worked. But I was
in several Facebook groups for people in
similar situations all around the world.
And what I heard was that at that time
in early 2022
most patients in America in the
situation my mom was in were being sent
straight to hospice. Their doctors
didn't know about that regimen for that
indication.
But today anyone anywhere in the world
suffering from that cancer or their
loved one
can put the same clinical history into
the free tier of GPT-5 and it will
recommend that regimen.
So the diffusion of medical expertise,
life-saving know-how from a handful of
oncologists in the world to anyone who
needs it
in the space of 3 years
is truly profound. Heartening and I
would say somewhat desensitizing. Yeah,
I know that's that's very powerful and I
would second that the the excitement
that I have about developments we've
already seen in in health care. A few
weeks ago, I was working with a
a group where that's preparing a new
Catholic medical school and we were
talking a lot about how do we leverage
the technology to create an ever more
preventative, precise, personalized, and
accessible uh health care system while
at the same time keeping our rich
patrimony of humanistic formation so
that
all health care professionals can devote
appropriate time for empathetic and
compassionate care. If we get things
right we will be able to make these
kinds of you know life-saving or just
profoundly transformative uh treatments
more available especially to the the
marginalized, those who have been
unjustly deprived of health care in the
past. We'll make that more accessible.
We'll advance in our our diagnostics,
which we've already done. We'll be able
to help people care for themselves
better. We'll actually empower patients
to to take uh
greater control and direction over their
own well-being. Uh and again, if we get
this right and we don't fall into a kind
of dehumanizing market mentality of
hyper-efficiency, it actually free up a
lot of medical professionals say for
instance just to spend less time
attentive to typing away at a onerous uh
detailed medical report.
Leveraging AI technology to facilitate
that kind of reporting so that they can
be more present, more attentive, and
maybe deliver the hard news that will
still come. You know, we may not be able
to cure every disease immediately, but
the the hard news that will still come
will be delivered with that care and
that attention. Uh so I I think the the
Catholic Church in particular and in
collaboration with a lot of good other
good people in the world can really
bring us to a new level
of of health care if we think through it
well and we prepare well. Uh I was also
blessed to take part yesterday in the
forum session on AI and education. And
something we were looking about are some
of these initial experiments in the
so-called Alpha school model, which is
very much focused on roughly 2 hours of
AI-assisted education that's very much
focused on say standard maths and uh
literary exercises that really help
students toward a kind of mastery.
Right? Cuz we've we already see
throughout the world a kind of
industrial model of education and you do
you do your knowledge dump on your 30 or
40 or in some universities
300 students and if they more or less
get it and they stick around and
persevere, they'll be moved forward. But
no one really has the time and the
energy with the exception of some very
elite schools to really ensure a a
personalized attention to each student
to see, "Okay, you really mastered that,
so let's move on." Or "You really
mastered that quickly, so let's get you
ahead."
If if we can leverage this technology
the way that perhaps imperfectly the
Alpha schools are already doing in that
2-hour instructional period, but we
combine that and integrate it with a
really full robust Catholic anthropology
of the human person and the person's
different dimensions including their
relationality well, that frees us up to
use so much time for conversations about
great books, for Socratic dialogue and
debate, for cooking, for dancing, for
hiking, for starting your own business
and and experimenting together in in
different group projects. Like
it's not about replacing these human
activities. Again, if we get AI right in
education, we could actually do a better
job of having more embodied, more
communal education for more people. But
again, we have to really think this
through and plan well and I'm glad that
people in the AI forum are doing this
now and and are charting a
a really potentially great future for us
in these areas. And uh Will, if if we
can turn to you, what what's giving you
hope? What would you what would you like
to see happen? I I think I'm
potentially, yeah, temperamentally less
optimistic than than these two, but I I
I am reassured and I'm actually
um
yeah, my my confidence has been improved
I think recently looking at this growing
movement of people from across faiths,
but in particularly within in the church
um
seeing both
the concerns that they need to respond
to um some of which are to do with
interacting with other other, you know,
fields and and sort of diplomatic uh
strategies we might we might think
about, but but others are responding to
the the spiritual um questions and
issues raised by these
uh by these AI systems and I I do think
it's it's worth saying as as well that
um
you know
I think the church is going to need to
think about um
the the spiritual sense of people's, you
know, souls being potentially uh at risk
from some of these chatbot in-
interactions and that's not a
conversation I'm hearing a lot. It's a
bit depressing. I think it goes beyond
sort of practical safety into the realm
of uh you know, spiritual past- past-
pastorship pastoralism. Um
but I I think
I do see a world in which the church
does respond to that and sees it, you
know, and actually comes out in a better
position than it was previously
precisely because all these questions
are being raised by AI, precisely
because people are fed up with their
online existence and their alienated
their alienation from the world and they
want more embodiment. Catholic Church
does embodiment pretty well. So I think
I you know, I think for myself and lots
of people I know have been drawn to the
faith partly through those through those
sort of physical
uh the sacraments and the community. So
that that I think is my my best stab at
an optimistic take.
Um I want to thank each and one of you
uh Will, Father Michael, and John Clark.
This has been a real joy. Uh thank you
for all the work that you're doing. It's
very inspiring. It's very important and
I hope that we can, you know, have this
conversation again in the future and see
where we're at. Uh thanks again. Thank
you.
>> Thank you.